http://www.theganggreen.com/privacy-policy

Episode 871 – Chronicles of Nania: Key Stats from Week 13 & Audio of Michael’s End of Game Reaction
Kyrie Irving’s media saga shows just how clueless he is
Pressure will start to mount on Jets’ foes: Don’t be that team
Jets fan Rich Eisen would love to woo Trevor Lawrence with wedding gift
New York Daily News abruptly withdraws Manish Mehta from the Jets beat
Daily News pulls Manish Mehta from Jets coverage amid bizarre ‘stalking’ scandal
How Frank Bush will handle Jets defense without Gregg Williams
Adam Gase ‘surprised’ Jamal Adams ripped him before Jets trade
Listen to Episode 55 of ‘Gang’s All Here’: Analyzing the Gregg Williams Firing feat. Eric Mangini
Denzel Mims will miss Jets vs. Seahawks due to family emergency
TheGangGreen.com Privacy Policy
It is TheGangGreen.com's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to https://www.theganggreen.com and https://forums.theganggreen.com (hereinafter, "us", "we", or TheGangGreen.com). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.
This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and Conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, TheGangGreen.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. TheGangGreen.com's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how TheGangGreen.com's visitors use its website. From time to time, TheGangGreen.com may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
TheGangGreen.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users posting comments on TheGangGreen.com Message Board . TheGangGreen.com only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to TheGangGreen.com's websites choose to interact with TheGangGreen.com in ways that require TheGangGreen.com to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that TheGangGreen.com gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for our Message Board at https://forums.theganggreen.com to provide a username and email address.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Advertisements
Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by TheGangGreen.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Links To External Sites
Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.
We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.
Aggregated Statistics
TheGangGreen.com may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. TheGangGreen.com may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, TheGangGreen.com does not disclose your personally-identifying information.
Cookies
To enrich and perfect your online experience, TheGangGreen.com uses "Cookies", similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. TheGangGreen.com uses cookies to help TheGangGreen.com identify and track visitors, their usage of https://www.theganggreen.com and https://forums.theganggreen.com, and their website access preferences. TheGangGreen.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using TheGangGreen.com's websites, with the drawback that certain features of TheGangGreen.com's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to TheGangGreen.com's use of cookies.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, TheGangGreen.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in TheGangGreen.com's sole discretion. TheGangGreen.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Credit & Contact Information
If you have any questions regarding TheGangGreen.com or our Privacy Policy, please contact us through the Contact Us page.
